# MANDA SHIVA REDDY

# SALESFORCE DEVELOPER

#### CONTACT

9182912375

mshivareddy@gmail.com

SKILLS

Configurations - Workflows, process Builder, Flows, Approval process, Record types, Security Model, Validations, Creating Profiles, Roles, Users, Page Layouts, Email templates, Reports & Dashboards.

**Customization** - Apex class, Apex trigger, Asynchronous Apex.

**Lightning Component** - Aura and Lightning Web Component (LWC).

\_\_\_\_\_

#### **EDUCATION**

National Institute of Technology, Kurukshetra

2019-2021 (M. Tech) Aggregate 9.3 CGPA

# Nalla Malla Reddy Engineering College

2015-2019 (B. Tech) Aggregate 80.1%

#### **Pratibha Junior College**

2013-2015 (12th) Aggregate 93.8%

#### St. Thomas High School

2012-2013 (10th) Aggregate 78%

# CERTIFICATIONS

- Salesforce Associate
- Platform Developer I
- CPQ Specialist

# PROFILE

To succeed in an environment of growth & excellence and earn a job which provides me job satisfaction and self-development which helps me to achieve personal as well as organizational goals. Have 1.5+ years of experience in the IT industry. In-depth Understanding of Configuration and Customization in Salesforce.

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

Salesforce Developer | NoblQ Solutions

(Jeevan Technologies Acquired By NoblQ Solutions)

Chennai - April 2024 - Current

Salesforce Developer | Jeevan Technologies

Chennai - April 2023 - March 2024

Salesforce Intern | Dev Rabbit IT Solutions

Tirupati – Jan 2023 - April 2023

Online Data Analyst | TELUS International AI

Remote – March 2022 – Feb 2022

#### **PROJECT**

# **Agency Workspace**

(April 2023 - Sep 2023)

## **Description:**

The goal of the Agency Workspace is to keep track of customer insurance information. The project was developed by community cloud so that the agent, agency, or customer can log in and make an Enrollment for the client with a variety of policies through the Benefit mall website.

## Responsibilities:

- Understanding the business requirements and developing Design and Solutions.
- Involved in development of SFDC Application using Apex classes, Apex Trigger.
  Worked on Asynchronous Apex Class, Data loader, Test class.
- Participated in Customer discussions and provided necessary clarifications to customers.
- Created Custom object, Custom field, role-based page layouts, workflow rule, Approval process, record types.
- Performed unit testing for User stories and bug fixes.

# Paradigm (Deloitte Project)

(Oct 2023 - Current)

## **Description:**

 Paradigm is a new global client and engagement acceptance solution developed on salesforce platform for guiding Deloitte businesses and risk professionals through single risk process.

# Responsibilities:

- Developed Apex classes and triggers, utilizing SOQL for efficient data queries and operations in Salesforce
- Developed Lightning Components and improved UI/UX by incorporating custom CSS and design parameters, enhancing overall functionality and user experience.
- Provided support and maintenance for Salesforce applications, troubleshooting and resolving issues for optimal performance.
- Tested developed solutions by creating and executing Apex test classes to ensure code quality and coverage.
- Created and maintained comprehensive technical documentation for developed solutions and processes.